

Aleksandr Beliun

Date of Birth: 09 March 1992

Nygade 17, 1. 8700 Horsens Mobile #: +45 50 36 93 62 +370 62970577 aleksandr.beliun @gmail.com aleksandr.beliun @aiesec.net

LinkedIn: AleksandrBeliun

Personal Profile

I am very interested in technology. Everything related to computers attracts me. Especially untraditional input devices and virtual reality experience. Technology is everywhere and I want to be a part of it.

As and IT student it is very important to continue to develop since it is very hard to choose a specific area when technology moves on every day. There are many different topics. Currently my focus is to continue to improve my programming skills.

Work Experience

12.2012 – 06.2014	JP Horsens V/Torben Karsberg, Horsens (Denmark) Deliverer
09.2011 – 05.2012	Allied Recruitment / Clipper Logistics, London (United Kingdom) Warehouse (picker / packer)

Education

08.2012 – Present	VIA University College Campus Horsens, Horsens (Denmark) ICT Engineering Programme
09.1999 – 06.2011	Visagino Draugystes vidurine mokykla (Lithuania) - Draugystes Secondary school of Visaginas, Visaginas (Lithuania)

IT-Skills

Platform	Android, Windows
Programs	Microsoft Office, Eclipse, Microsoft Visual Studio, Atmel AVR Studio, LTSpice, Wireshark, Astah, Eagle CAD PCB
Programming Languages	Java, Javascript, C/C#, microC, Assembly, SQL, XML, HTML, CSS with JQuerry
Development and Processing skills	SCRUM, Agile Unified Process(AUP), SWOT

Languages

Lithuanian Native Language

Russian Excellent

English Excellent

Danish Basic (Danish courses 2013-2014)

Job Skills

Once during my work in a warehouse I had to organise a group of processers when the proper merchandise did not arrive. I had to supply them with different merchandise for a different customer to process. Finding a proper set of products takes time and reflects on productivity. In the end of the day, we managed to process a significant amount to deliver to another customer.

Personal Skills

It takes time for me to accommodate with new people and environment, but result are worth it. New people always bring many opportunities.

I like to challenge myself from time to time with some exercise or a specific task. It can be hard but at the same time, it is fun.

Hobbies

I dedicate a lot of my free time to studies balancing between work, friends and personal benefits.

In daily life, I am very close to my small group of friends. We always do something interesting together like going to the beach or playing football.